

#### **EDUCATION**

- Ingeniería de Sistemas, Universidad de La Guajira
- Cloud engineer learning path, **Owiklabs**
- · Architecting with google cloud compute engine, coursera

#### LANGUAGES

• English: C1

• French: A2

• Spanish: Native

#### **CONTACTO**

mayberaim@gmail.com

Cel: 3147252133

<u>Mayber Antonio Illidge</u> in

<u>PointlessAIM</u>

Bogotá, Colombia

#### **SKILLS**

0

- Gcp
- Linux Scrum
- Cloud Architechture Django, FastApi
- Sql &NoSQL
- React
- Typescript
- AWS
- Flutter

- Collaborative Work
- Python
- Git, GitHub
- Java RestApis
- Dart
- Firebase
- Azure
- Angular

# **MAYBER ANTONIO** ILLIDGE MAFLA

SYSTEMS ENGINEER

#### **PROFILE**

Passionate full-stack developer with expertise in Angular, Flutter, React, Dart, Firebase, and Azure. Proven ability to build high-performance web and mobile applications, design and implement APIs, manage SQL and NoSQL databases, and leverage cloud platforms for scalable and cost-effective solutions. Strong communication and collaboration skills, with a passion for continuous learning and delivering cutting-edge solutions.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Developer Frontend Mobile**

Efficode, 2019 - 2024

Flutter, Mobile Apps (E-commerce, Social, Fitness), UX/UI, Performance (Battery, Speed), Dev Tools (Hot Reload, State Management), Gamification

#### **Developer Frontend Web**

Efficode, 2019 - 2024

Angular, Web Dev (UI/UX, PWAs, Cross-Platform), API Integration, Cloud (GCP, Azure, AWS), Performance, Scalability, SEO, Accessibility

## **Developer Backend**

Computic, 2018 - 2020

REST API Development, OAuth, Security, Load Balancing, Rate Limiting, High Availability, Fault Tolerance, Cloud Deployment, Autoscaling, Self-Monitoring, Business Focus

#### **EDUCACIÓN**

- Ingeniería de Sistemas, Universidad de La Guajira
- <u>Certificación Associate Cloud</u>
  <u>Engineer</u>, Qwiklabs

#### LANGUAGES

- English: B1
- Spanish: Native

#### CONTACTO



mariofernandogonsalvez@gm





Cel: +573209318053



Mario Gonsalvez



Wafer2000



Colombia

#### **HABILIDADES**

- GCP
- Cloud Architechture
- Sql &NoSQL
- AWS
- Flutter
- Collaborative Work
- FastApi
- Git, GitHub
- Dart
- Firebase
- Clean Code
- Design Patterns

# MARIO FERNANDO GONSALVEZ ARIAS

# INGENIERO DE SISTEMAS

#### **PERFIL**

Desarrollador apasionado de front-end con experiencia en Angular, Flutter, Nextjs, Dart, Firebase y Google. Capacidad demostrada para crear aplicaciones web y móviles de alto rendimiento, diseñar e implementar API, administrar bases de datos SQL y NoSQL y aprovechar plataformas en la nube para obtener soluciones escalables y rentables. Sólidas habilidades de comunicación y colaboración, con pasión por el aprendizaje continuo y la entrega de soluciones de vanguardia.

#### **EXPERIENCIA**

#### Desarrollador Flutter Mobile

Periferia IT Group, 2024 - actualmente

Flutter, Bloc, Git, Azure DevOps, APIs Restful, Riverpod, GCP, Firebase, UI/UX, Copilot, IA, Websockets, SQLite (Local), Android, iOS, App Store, Play Store, BLoC, Provider.

#### Preventa GCP

Servinformacion, 2022 - 2024

GCP, AWS, Azure, Google Workspace, BigData, Docker y Kubernetes

#### Desarrollador Frontend Mobile/Web

Efficode, 2018 - 2022

Flutter, Mobile Apps (E-commerce, Social, Fitness), UX/UI, Performance (Battery, Speed), Dev Tools (Hot Reload, State Management), Gamification, HTML5, CSS3, ES6+, Firebase. AWS, Angular, Typescript.

#### **EDUCATION**

- Systems Engineering, University of La Guajira
- Cloud engineer learning path,
  Qwiklabs
- Architecting with google cloud compute engine, coursera

#### LANGUAGES

- English: B1
- Spanish: Native

#### CONTACT



mariofernandogonsalvez@gm



Cel: +573209318053



Mario Gonsalvez



Wafer2000



Colombia

#### SKILLS

- GCP
- Cloud Architechture
- Sal &NoSQL
- AWS
- Flutter
- Collaborative Work
- FastApi
- Git, GitHub
- Dart
- Firebase
- Clean Code
- Design Patterns

# MARIO FERNANDO GONSALVEZ ARIAS

# SYSTEMS ENGINEER

#### **PROFILE**

Passionate FrontEnd developer with expertise in Angular, Flutter, Nextjs, Dart, Firebase, and Google. Proven ability to build high-performance web and mobile applications, design and implement APIs, manage SQL and NoSQL databases, and leverage cloud platforms for scalable and cost-effective solutions. Strong communication and collaboration skills, with a passion for continuous learning and delivering cutting-edge solutions.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Developer Flutter Mobile

Periferia IT Group, 2024 - actually

Flutter, Bloc, Git, Azure DevOps, APIs Restful, Riverpod, GCP, Firebase, UI/UX, Copilot, IA, Websockets, SQLite (Local), Android, iOS, App Store, Play Store, BLoC, Provider.

#### Presales GCP

Servinformacion, 2022 - 2024

GCP, AWS, Azure, Google Workspace, Data

## Developer Frontend Mobile

Efficode, 2018 - 2022

Flutter, Mobile Apps (E-commerce, Social, Fitness), UX/UI, Performance (Battery, Speed), Dev Tools (Hot Reload, State Management), Gamification, HTML5, CSS3, ES6+, Firebase. AWS, Angular, Typescript.

#### **EDUCATION**

- Systems Engineering, University of La Guajira
- Architecting with google cloud compute engine, coursera

#### LANGUAGES

- English: C1
- Spanish: Native

#### CONTACT

immyjosemazogonzalez@gmail.com

Cel: +573003448631

in <u>Jimmy Mazo</u>

Colombia

#### SKILLS

- GCP
- Sql & NoSQL
- AWS
- Dart
- Flutter
- FastApi
- Git, GitHub
- Firebase
- Clean Code
- Design Patterns
- Collaborative Work

# JIMMY JOSE MAZO GONZALEZ

SYSTEMS ENGINEER

#### **PROFILE**

Passionate FrontEnd developer with expertise in Angular, Flutter, Dart, Firebase, and Google. Proven ability to build high-performance web and mobile applications, design and implement APIs, manage SQL and NoSQL databases, and leverage cloud platforms for scalable and cost-effective solutions. Strong communication and collaboration skills, with a passion for continuous learning and delivering cutting-edge solutions.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Developer Frontend Mobile

Efficode, 2021 - At The Moment

Flutter, Mobile Apps (E-commerce, Social, Fitness), UX/UI, Performance (Battery, Speed), Dev Tools (Hot Reload, State Management), Gamification, HTML5, CSS3, ES6+, Firebase. AWS, Angular, Typescript, Websockets.